They ended up going to see a ghost movie
.
I just watched the Hollywood film Insidious Out of Borderlands, which is currently running in theaters with Tamil dubbing.   Please
subscribe to the channel before going into the video.  I
liked this picture.
The film runs on the usual Insidious Door concept
.  But this time, it was a little
different,
like demons were coming to the real world.   There aren't
many adult scenes in the film
.  But if you
buy snacks and go there thinking you can eat something, you wo
n't be able to sit down and eat.  There
are so many disgusting scenes in the film.
Insidious fans, horror fans, will
definitely like this movie.
Especially in the climax, they ended everything
well with a twist
.  A decent horror
movie is the only one you can try in the theater.
Those who have seen the film, please
leave your thoughts in the comments on how you liked the film.  Boy